O  IN    In
O  NN    addition
O  ,    ,
B-ORG  NNP    Farley
O  NNS    representatives
O  VBD    were
O  VBG    negotiating
O  NNP    Wednesday
O  IN    with
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    Georgia
O  NNP    Secretary
O  POS    's
O  NN    office
O  TO    to
O  NN    answer
O  NNS    concerns
O  VBN    raised
O  IN    about
O  DT    the
O  NN    deal
O  POS    's
O  NN    financing
O  .    .



B-ORG  NNP    Farley
O  ,    ,
O  NN    manufacturer
O  IN    of
O  NNP    Fruit
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NNP    Loom
O  NN    underwear
O  CC    and
O  NNP    Acme
O  NNS    boots
O  ,    ,
O  VBZ    owns
O  CD    9.8
O  NN    percent
O  ,    ,
O  CC    or
O  CD    2.9
O  CD    million
O  NNS    shares
O  ,    ,
O  IN    of
B-ORG  NNP    Pepperell
O  NN    stock
O  .    .


O  NN    Today
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    company
O  VBD    said
O  RB    approximately
O  CD    14
O  CD    million
O  NNS    shares
O  VBD    had
O  VBN    been
O  VBN    tendered
O  ,    ,
O  WDT    which
O  MD    would
O  VB    give
O  DT    the
O  JJ    Chicago-based
O  NN    conglomerate
O  NN    control
O  IN    of
O  IN    about
O  CD    57
O  NN    percent
O  IN    of
B-ORG  NNP    Pepperell
O  NNS    shares
O  ,    ,
O  RB    well
O  RB    short
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  JJ    two-thirds
O  NN    requirement
O  IN    on
O  WDT    which
O  DT    the
O  NN    offer
O  VBZ    is
O  JJ    contingent
O  .    .


B-PER  NNP    Pepperell
O  VBD    told
O  DT    the
O  VBZ    appeals
O  NN    court
O  IN    that
B-PER  NNP    Tidwell
O  VBD    was
O  JJ    incorrect
O  WRB    when
O  PRP    he
O  VBD    ruled
O  IN    that
B-PER  NNP    Pepperell
O  VBD    had
O  DT    no
O  JJ    legal
O  NN    standing
O  TO    to
O  VB    question
O  DT    the
O  NN    amount
O  IN    of
O  NN    debt
O  VBN    contained
O  IN    in
B-ORG  NNP    Farley
O  POS    's
O  NN    offer
O  CC    and
O  IN    that
B-PER  NNP    Farley
O  POS    's
O  JJ    financial
O  NN    adviser
O  ,    ,
B-ORG  NNP    Drexel
I-ORG  NNP    Burnham
I-ORG  NNP    Lambert
I-ORG  NNP    Inc.
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    was
O  RB    not
O  VBN    bound
O  IN    by
O  DT    an
O  NN    agreement
O  VBG    barring
O  NN    disclosure
O  IN    of
O  JJ    confidential
O  NN    information
O  VBN    obtained
O  IN    during
B-PER  NNP    Pepperell
O  POS    's
O  NN    acquisition
O  IN    of
B-ORG  NNP    J.P.
I-ORG  NNP    Stevens
I-ORG  NN    &amp
I-ORG  :    ;



B-PER  NNP    Drexel
O  NN    attorney
B-PER  NNP    Lawrence
I-PER  NNP    Silverman
O  VBD    said
O  DT    the
O  NN    investment
O  NN    firm
O  VBD    was
O  RB    not
O  VBN    bound
O  IN    by
O  DT    the
O  JJ    standstill
O  NN    agreement
O  IN    between
B-ORG  NNP    Odyssey
I-ORG  NNPS    Partners
O  ,    ,
O  WDT    which
B-PER  NNP    Drexel
O  VBD    advised
O  ,    ,
O  CC    and
B-ORG  NNP    J.P.
I-ORG  NNP    Stevens
O  .    .


B-ORG  NNP    Pepperell
O  VBD    became
O  DT    the
O  NN    nation
O  POS    's
O  JJS    largest
O  RB    publicly
O  VBN    held
O  JJ    textile
O  NN    company
O  IN    through
O  DT    a
O  JJ    joint
O  NN    deal
O  IN    with
B-ORG  NNP    Odyssey
I-ORG  NNPS    Partners
O  TO    to
O  VB    acquire
B-ORG  NNP    Stevens
O  .    .


O  IN    In
O  DT    any
O  NN    case
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Silverman
O  VBD    said
B-PER  NNP    Drexel
O  VBD    had
O  VBN    divulged
O  DT    no
O  JJ    confidential
O  NN    information
O  TO    to
B-ORG  NNP    Farley
O  .    .


O  IN    Outside
O  DT    the
O  NN    courtroom
O  ,    ,
B-ORG  NNP    Farley
O  POS    's
B-PER  NNP    Greiner
O  VBD    said
O  PRP    he
O  VBD    did
O  RB    not
O  VB    know
O  WP    what
O  NNS    negotiations
O  VBD    were
O  VBG    going
O  IN    on
O  IN    between
B-ORG  NNP    Farley
O  CC    and
B-ORG  NNP    Cleland
O  ,    ,
O  WP    who
O  JJ    last
O  NNP    Friday
O  VBD    ordered
O  DT    the
O  NN    company
O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  TO    to
O  VB    provide
O  NN    assurance
O  :    ...
O  IN    that
O  DT    the
O  NNS    shareholders
O  IN    of
B-ORG  NNP    West
I-ORG  NNP    Point
O  MD    will
O  VB    be
O  RB    fully
O  VBN    informed
O  IN    as
O  TO    to
O  DT    the
O  NNS    risks
O  VBN    associated
O  IN    with
O  DT    both
O  VBG    accepting
O  CC    and
O  VBG    rejecting
O  DT    the
B-ORG  NNP    Farley
O  NN    tender
O  NN    offer.
O  ''    '
O  ''    '



O  DT    The
O  NN    drop
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    blamed
O  IN    on
O  NN    $17
O  CD    million
O  IN    in
O  JJ    special
O  NNS    charges
O  ,    ,
O  VBG    including
O  NN    $3
O  CD    million
O  VBN    incurred
O  IN    in
O  VBG    fighting
B-ORG  NNP    Farley
O  .    .


O  PP$    Its
O  JJ    first-quarter
O  NN    revenue
O  VBD    rose
O  CD    42
O  NN    percent
O  TO    to
O  NN    $683.1
O  CD    million
O  IN    from
O  NN    $481
O  CD    million
O  DT    a
O  NN    year
O  RB    earlier
O  .    .


O  DT    The
B-ORG  NNP    Chicago
I-ORG  NNP    Board
I-ORG  IN    of
I-ORG  NNP    Trade
O  VBZ    has
O  VBN    fined
O  CC    and
O  VBN    suspended
O  CD    six
O  NNS    men
O  VBN    linked
O  TO    to
O  DT    a
O  NN    scheme
O  IN    in
O  WDT    which
O  DT    a
O  NN    trader
O  VBD    donned
O  DT    a
O  NN    wig
O  CC    and
O  VBD    used
O  JJ    fake
O  NN    identification
O  TO    to
O  VB    access
O  JJ    privileged
O  NN    information
O  ,    ,
B-ORG  NNP    CBOT
O  NNS    officials
O  VBD    said
O  NN    today
O  .    .


O  DT    The
O  CD    six
B-ORG  NNP    CBOT
O  NNS    members
O  VBD    were
O  VBN    fined
O  IN    between
O  NN    $5
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  CC    and
O  NN    $50
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  DT    each
O  CC    and
O  VBN    suspended
O  IN    for
O  NNS    periods
O  VBG    ranging
O  IN    from
O  CD    15
O  NNS    days
O  TO    to
O  CD    10
O  NNS    years
O  .    .


O  DT    The
O  NNS    traders
O  VBD    were
O  VBN    linked
O  IN    through
O  JJ    federal
O  NN    court
O  NN    testimony
O  JJ    last
O  NN    summer
O  TO    to
O  DT    the
O  NN    wig
O  NN    scheme
O  VBD    masterminded
O  IN    by
O  JJ    veteran
O  NN    trader
B-PER  NNP    Thompson
I-PER  NNP    B.
I-PER  NNP    Sanders
O  .    .


B-PER  NNP    Sanders
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    sentenced
O  JJ    last
O  NNP    November
O  TO    to
O  CD    six
O  NNS    years
O  IN    in
O  NN    prison
O  .    .


O  DT    The
O  JJ    disciplinary
O  NNS    moves
O  IN    by
O  DT    the
O  NN    board
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    imposed
O  NNP    Dec.
O  CD    16
O  CC    but
O  VBD    announced
O  DT    this
O  NN    week
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    followed
O  NNS    revelations
O  IN    by
O  NNS    prosecutors
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
B-PER  NNP    Sanders
O  NN    probe
O  .    .



O  DT    The
O  NN    government
O  VBD    claimed
O  IN    that
O  IN    because
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NNS    disguises
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Sanders
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Dewey
O  CC    and
O  NNS    others
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NN    scheme
O  VBD    were
O  JJ    able
O  TO    to
O  VB    claim
O  NN    $30
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  IN    in
O  NN    trading
O  NNS    profits
O  IN    without
O  NN    detection
O  .    .


O  DT    The
O  CD    six
O  VBN    suspended
O  NNS    traders
O  VBD    were
O  VBN    identified
O  IN    as
B-PER  NNP    David
I-PER  NNP    Schremser
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Dan
I-PER  NNP    Hayes
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Patrick
I-PER  NNP    Bratta
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Scott
I-PER  NNP    Bremner
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Patrick
I-PER  NNP    Sutor
O  CC    and
B-PER  NNP    Robert
I-PER  NNP    Kinkade
O  .    .


B-PER  NNP    Schremser
O  CC    and
B-PER  NNP    Hayes
O  VBD    testified
O  IN    under
O  NNS    grants
O  IN    of
O  NN    immunity
O  IN    from
O  NN    prosecution
O  IN    at
B-PER  NNP    Sanders
O  POS    '
O  NN    trial
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
B-ORG  NNP    CBOT
O  VBD    said
O  .    .


O  DT    The
B-ORG  NNP    CBOT
O  NN    board
O  IN    of
O  NNS    governors
O  VBD    imposed
O  DT    a
O  JJ    10-year
O  NN    suspension
O  IN    on
B-PER  NNP    Bremner
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    fined
O  PRP    him
O  NN    $50
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  CC    and
O  VBD    barred
O  PRP    him
O  IN    from
O  VBG    associating
O  IN    with
O  JJ    other
O  NNS    members
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    exchange
O  IN    during
O  DT    the
O  NN    suspension
O  .    .


B-PER  NNP    Bretta
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    suspended
O  IN    for
O  CD    four
O  NNS    years
O  CC    and
O  VBN    fined
O  NN    $25
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  .    .


B-PER  NNP    Hayes
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    suspended
O  IN    for
O  CD    two
O  NNS    years
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Sutor
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    suspended
O  IN    for
O  CD    six
O  NNS    months
O  CC    and
O  VBN    fined
O  NN    $10
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  .    .


B-PER  NN    Kinkade
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    suspended
O  IN    for
O  CD    four
O  NNS    months
O  CC    and
O  VBN    fined
O  NN    $10
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  CC    and
B-PER  NNP    Schremser
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    suspended
O  IN    for
O  CD    15
O  NNS    days
O  CC    and
O  VBN    fined
O  NN    $5
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  .    .



O  NNP    Union
O  NNP    Boss
O  VBZ    Says
O  NNS    Guns
O  NNP    Found
O  IN    After
O  NNP    Shootout
O  VBD    Were
O  NNP    Smuggled
O  IN    From
B-LOC  NNP    U.S
I-LOC  .    .


O  IN    By
B-PER  NNP    ANITA
I-PER  NNP    SNOW


B-ORG  NNP    Associated
I-ORG  NNP    Press
O  NNP    Writer


B-LOC  NNP    MEXICO
I-LOC  NNP    CITY
O  -LRB-    -LRB-
B-ORG  NNP    AP
O  -RRB-    -RRB-


O  DT    The
O  NN    arrest
O  NNP    Tuesday
O  IN    of
B-PER  NNP    Joaquin
I-PER  NNP    Hernandez
I-PER  NNP    Galicia
O  VBD    prompted
O  NNS    strikes
O  IN    by
O  NN    union
O  NNS    members
O  IN    that
O  VBD    crippled
O  DT    the
O  NN    country
O  POS    's
O  VBN    nationalized
O  NN    oil
O  NN    industry
O  IN    for
O  DT    a
O  NN    day
O  CC    but
O  VBD    ended
O  NNP    Wednesday
O  IN    at
O  DT    a
O  NN    behest
O  IN    of
O  DT    a
O  NN    union
O  NN    official
O  .    .


B-PER  NNP    Hernandez
I-PER  NNP    Galicia
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    charged
O  NN    today
O  IN    before
O  JJ    penal
O  NN    judge
B-PER  NNP    Jose
I-PER  NNP    Luis
I-PER  NNP    Garcia
I-PER  NNP    Vasco
O  ,    ,
O  WP    who
O  VBZ    has
O  CD    72
O  NNS    hours
O  TO    to
O  VB    decide
O  IN    whether
O  DT    the
O  VBN    accused
O  MD    should
O  VB    be
O  VBN    released
O  IN    on
O  NN    bail
O  .    .


O  IN    On
O  NNP    Wednesday
O  NN    night
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Hernanadez
I-PER  NNP    Galicia
O  VBD    claimed
O  DT    the
O  CD    200
O  NNP    Uzi
O  NN    machine
O  NNS    guns
O  VBN    seized
O  IN    in
O  DT    an
O  NN    assault
O  IN    on
O  PP$    his
O  NN    home
O  VBD    were
O  VBN    smuggled
O  IN    from
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    United
I-LOC  NNPS    States
O  CC    and
O  VBN    needed
O  IN    by
O  NN    union
O  NNS    leaders
O  IN    for
O  NN    self-defense
O  ,    ,
O  NNS    officials
O  VBD    said
O  .    .


O  IN    At
O  JJS    least
O  CD    50
O  NNS    associates
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    union
O  NN    boss
O  VBN    arrested
O  IN    with
O  PRP    him
O  NNP    Tuesday
O  NN    face
O  VBZ    charges
O  IN    of
O  NN    fraud
O  ,    ,
O  NNS    weapons
O  CC    and
O  NN    tax
O  NN    evasion
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    said
B-PER  NNP    Fernando
I-PER  NNP    Arias
I-PER  NNP    Perez
O  ,    ,
O  DT    a
O  NN    spokesman
O  IN    for
O  DT    the
O  NN    attorney
O  POS    's
O  NN    office
O  .    .


O  DT    A
O  NN    source
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NN    office
O  ,    ,
O  WP    who
O  VBD    spoke
O  IN    on
O  NN    condition
O  IN    of
O  NN    anonymity
O  ,    ,
O  RB    also
O  VBD    said
O  IN    that
O  CD    two
O  IN    of
B-PER  NNP    Hernandez
I-PER  NNP    Galicia
O  POS    's
O  NNS    bodyguards
O  IN    on
O  NNP    Wednesday
O  VBD    accused
O  PP$    their
O  NN    boss
O  IN    of
O  VBG    ordering
O  DT    the
O  CD    1983
O  NN    slaying
O  IN    of
O  DT    a
O  NN    mayor
O  WP    who
O  VBD    headed
O  DT    a
O  NN    union
O  JJ    local
O  .    .


O  NNS    Tensions
O  VB    have
O  RB    long
O  VBN    run
O  JJ    high
O  IN    between
B-PER  NNP    Hernandez
I-PER  NNP    Galicia
O  CC    and
O  RB    newly
O  VBN    inaugurated
O  NNP    President
B-PER  NNP    Carlos
I-PER  NNP    Salinas
I-PER  NNP    de
I-PER  NNP    Gortari
O  ,    ,
O  WP    who
O  VBZ    has
O  VBN    pledged
O  TO    to
O  VB    sell
O  CC    or
O  VB    close
O  JJ    unprofitable
O  CC    or
O  JJ    non-strategic
O  NN    state
O  NNS    industries
O  .    .



B-LOC  NNP    Mexico
O  VBZ    is
O  DT    the
O  NN    world
O  POS    's
O  JJ    sixth-largest
O  JJ    crude
O  NN    oil
O  NN    producer
O  ,    ,
O  CC    and
O  NN    production
O  IN    from
O  DT    the
O  NN    country
O  POS    's
O  CD    nine
O  NNS    refineries
O  VBZ    amounts
O  TO    to
O  CD    1.4
O  CD    million
O  NNS    barrels
O  DT    a
O  NN    day
O  .    .


B-PER  NNP    Victor
I-PER  NNP    de
I-PER  NNP    Leon
O  ,    ,
O  VBG    acting
O  NN    coordinator
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    union
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    said
O  DT    the
O  JJ    back-to-work
O  NN    appeal
O  VBD    had
O  VBN    come
O  IN    from
B-PER  NNP    Salvador
I-PER  NNP    Barragan
I-PER  NNP    Camacho
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    union
O  POS    's
O  NN    secretary-general
O  IN    until
O  NNP    Wednesday
O  .    .



O  NNP    Weapons
O  VBD    were
O  VBN    found
O  IN    at
B-PER  NNP    Barragan
I-PER  NNP    Camacho
O  POS    's
O  NN    home
O  CC    and
O  PRP    he
O  VBD    was
O  IN    under
O  NN    arrest
O  ,    ,
O  NNS    officials
O  VBD    said
O  .    .


B-PER  NNP    Hernandez
I-PER  NNP    Galicia
O  VBD    told
O  NNS    investigators
O  DT    the
O  NNP    Uzis
O  CC    and
O  IN    about
O  CD    30
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  NNS    cartridges
O  VBD    were
O  RB    secretly
O  VBN    delivered
O  TO    to
O  PRP    him
O  IN    on
O  NNP    Dec.
O  CD    10
O  IN    by
O  JJ    former
O  NNP    Reynosa
O  NNP    Mayor
B-PER  NNP    Jose
I-PER  NNP    Cruz
I-PER  NNP    Contreras
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    attorney
O  POS    's
O  NN    office
O  VBD    said
O  IN    in
O  DT    a
O  NN    statement
O  .    .


B-PER  NNP    Hernandez
I-PER  NNP    Galicia
O  VBD    said
O  DT    the
O  NNS    arms
O  VBD    were
O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  TO    to
O  VB    defend
O  PP$    his
O  NN    union
O  NNS    members
O  ,    ,
O  VBN    given
O  DT    the
O  VBG    existing
O  NN    situation
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NN    country
O  ,    ,
O  ''    '
O  ''    '
O  DT    the
O  NN    statement
O  VBD    said
O  .    .


O  DT    The
O  NN    government
O  VBZ    has
O  RB    not
O  VBD    said
O  WP    what
O  PRP    it
O  VBZ    thinks
B-PER  NNP    Hernandez
I-PER  NNP    Galicia
O  VBD    planned
O  TO    to
O  VB    do
O  IN    with
O  DT    the
O  NNS    weapons
O  .    .


B-PER  NNP    Hernandez
I-PER  NNP    Galicia
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    arrested
O  WRB    when
O  NNS    soldiers
O  VBD    blew
O  RP    down
O  PP$    his
O  NN    door
O  IN    with
O  DT    a
O  NN    bazooka
O  IN    in
O  DT    a
O  NN    raid
O  IN    on
O  PP$    his
B-LOC  NNP    Ciudad
I-LOC  NNP    Madero
O  NN    home
O  .    .


O  DT    A
O  NN    spokesman
O  IN    for
O  DT    the
O  NN    attorney
O  POS    's
O  NN    office
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Felipe
I-PER  NNP    Flores
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    said
O  DT    a
O  NN    paraffin
O  NN    test
O  VBD    performed
O  IN    on
B-PER  NNP    Hernandez
I-PER  NNP    Galicia
O  VBD    showed
O  PRP    he
O  VBD    had
O  VBN    fired
O  DT    a
O  NN    gun
O  .    .


O  IN    In
O  PP$    his
O  NN    statement
O  TO    to
O  NNS    investigators
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Hernandez
I-PER  NNP    Galicia
O  VBD    argued
O  IN    that
O  NN    security
O  NNS    forces
O  VBD    had
O  DT    no
O  NN    right
O  TO    to
O  VB    force
O  PP$    their
O  NN    way
O  IN    into
O  PP$    his
O  NN    home
O  .    .


O  PRP    He
O  VBD    said
O  PRP    he
O  VBD    had
O  VBN    planned
O  TO    to
O  VB    distribute
O  DT    some
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NNP    Uzis
O  TO    to
O  JJ    other
O  NN    oil
O  NN    union
O  NNS    leaders
O  CC    and
O  VBD    said
B-PER  NNP    Cruz
I-PER  NNP    Contreras
O  ,    ,
O  WP    whom
O  PRP    he
O  VBD    described
O  IN    as
O  DT    a
O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  JJ    good
O  NN    friend
O  ,    ,
O  ''    '
O  ''    '
O  VBD    did
O  RB    not
O  VB    charge
O  PRP    him
O  IN    for
O  DT    the
O  NNS    weapons
O  CC    and
O  NN    ammunition
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    attorney
O  POS    's
O  NN    office
O  VBD    said
O  .    .


O  PRP    It
O  VBD    did
O  RB    not
O  VB    say
O  WRB    where
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    United
I-LOC  NNPS    States
O  DT    the
O  NNS    arms
O  VBD    were
O  VBN    bought
O  .    .


B-LOC  NNP    PURCHASE
O  ,    ,
B-LOC  NNP    N.Y
I-LOC  .    .


B-ORG  NNP    International
I-ORG  NNP    Paper
I-ORG  NNP    Co.
O  ,    ,
O  WDT    which
O  VBD    posted
O  DT    a
O  NN    record
O  CD    85
O  NN    percent
O  NN    increase
O  IN    in
O  CD    1988
O  NN    profit
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    announced
O  NNP    Thursday
O  PRP    it
O  VBZ    plans
O  TO    to
O  VB    launch
O  DT    a
O  NN    takeover
O  NN    bid
O  IN    for
B-LOC  NNP    Europe
O  POS    's
O  JJS    largest
O  NN    paper
O  NN    maker
O  .    .



O  CC    But
B-LOC  NNP    Paris
O  NN    stock
O  NNS    analysts
O  VBD    estimated
O  DT    the
O  NN    bid
O  IN    at
O  CD    650
O  TO    to
O  CD    700
O  JJ    French
O  NNS    francs
O  IN    per
O  VBP    share
O  NN    _
O  DT    the
O  NN    equivalent
O  IN    of
O  NN    $104
O  TO    to
O  NN    $113
O  VBN    based
O  IN    on
O  NNP    Thursday
O  POS    's
O  NN    exchange
O  NNS    rates
O  .    .



B-ORG  NNP    International
I-ORG  NNP    Paper
O  VBZ    is
O  DT    the
O  NN    world
O  POS    's
O  JJS    largest
O  NN    manufacturer
O  IN    of
O  NN    paper
O  CC    and
O  NN    paper
O  NNS    products
O  ,    ,
O  IN    with
O  JJ    primary
O  NN    production
O  NNS    facilities
O  IN    in
B-LOC  NNP    Maine
O  CC    and
O  IN    throughout
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NN    South
O  CC    and
O  NN    packaging
O  NNS    plants
O  IN    in
B-LOC  NNP    Europe
O  ,    ,
B-LOC  NNP    Asia
O  CC    and
B-LOC  NNP    South
I-LOC  NNP    America
O  .    .


O  IN    In
O  NN    addition
O  TO    to
O  DT    all
O  NNS    types
O  IN    of
O  NN    business
O  NN    paper
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    company
O  VBZ    makes
O  NN    milk
O  NNS    cartons
O  ,    ,
O  NN    bottle
O  NNS    labels
O  CC    and
O  JJ    corrugated
O  NNS    boxes
O  .    .


B-ORG  NNP    International
I-ORG  NNP    Paper
O  VBD    announced
O  RBR    earlier
O  DT    this
O  NN    week
O  IN    that
O  JJ    preliminary
O  NNS    figures
O  VBP    show
O  PP$    its
O  NNS    earnings
O  VBD    soared
O  JJ    last
O  NN    year
O  ,    ,
O  JJ    due
O  TO    to
O  JJ    strong
O  NN    demand
O  CC    and
O  JJ    high
O  VBG    operating
O  NN    capacity
O  .    .


O  IN    For
O  DT    the
O  CD    12
O  NNS    months
O  VBD    ended
O  JJ    last
O  NNP    Dec.
O  CD    31
O  ,    ,
B-ORG  NNP    International
I-ORG  NNP    Paper
O  VBD    said
O  PP$    its
O  JJ    net
O  NN    income
O  VBD    totaled
O  NN    $754
O  CD    million
O  ,    ,
O  CC    or
O  NN    $6.57
O  DT    a
O  NN    share
O  ,    ,
O  IN    up
O  IN    from
O  NN    $407
O  CD    million
O  ,    ,
O  CC    or
O  NN    $3.68
O  DT    a
O  NN    share
O  ,    ,
O  IN    in
O  CD    1987
O  .    .



O  DT    The
O  NN    company
O  VBD    reported
O  IN    that
O  PP$    its
O  NN    fourth-quarter
O  NN    net
O  NNS    earnings
O  VBD    jumped
O  CD    65
O  NN    percent
O  TO    to
O  NN    $206
O  CD    million
O  ,    ,
O  CC    or
O  NN    $1.81
O  DT    a
O  NN    share
O  ,    ,
O  IN    on
O  NNS    sales
O  IN    of
O  NN    $2.5
O  CD    billion
O  .    .



B-PER  NNP    Georges
O  VBD    said
O  IN    that
O  IN    for
O  DT    the
O  JJ    second
O  NN    year
O  IN    in
O  DT    a
O  NN    row
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    company
O  POS    's
O  NN    paper
O  CC    and
O  NN    paperboard
O  NNS    mills
O  VBN    operated
O  IN    at
O  CC    or
O  IN    near
O  NN    capacity
O  .    .


B-PER  NNP    Georges
O  VBD    said
O  DT    the
O  NN    company
O  VBD    planned
O  TO    to
O  VB    invest
O  NN    $900
O  CD    million
O  IN    in
O  CD    1989
O  TO    to
O  RB    further
O  VB    modernize
O  PP$    its
O  NNS    facilities
O  CC    and
O  MD    would
O  VB    continue
O  TO    to
O  VB    search
O  IN    for
O  JJ    new
O  NN    investment
O  NNS    opportunities
O  .    .


O  IN    For
O  NNP    Release
O  NNP    Weekend
O  NNP    Editions
O  NNP    Jan.
O  CD    14-15
O  CC    and
O  RB    Thereafter


O  IN    By
B-PER  NNP    GEORGE
I-PER  NNP    BOEHMER


B-ORG  NNP    Associated
I-ORG  NNP    Press
O  NNP    Writer


B-LOC  NNP    GIESSEN
O  ,    ,
B-LOC  NNP    West
I-LOC  NNP    Germany
O  -LRB-    -LRB-
B-ORG  NNP    AP
O  -RRB-    -RRB-


O  DT    The
O  NN    maker
O  IN    of
O  NNP    Minox
O  JJ    miniature
O  NNS    cameras
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  NN    spy
O  NNS    cameras
O  POS    '
O  ''    '
O  VBN    made
O  JJ    famous
O  IN    in
O  DT    an
O  JJ    early
B-PER  NNP    James
I-PER  NNP    Bond
O  NN    movie
O  ,    ,
O  VBZ    has
O  VBN    racked
O  IN    up
O  JJ    big
O  NNS    losses
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    sought
O  JJ    bankruptcy-court
O  NN    protection
O  CC    and
O  VB    cut
O  PP$    its
O  NN    workforce
O  IN    by
O  CD    50
O  NN    percent
O  IN    in
O  DT    a
O  NN    struggle
O  TO    to
O  VB    stay
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NNP    Japanese-dominated
O  NN    market
O  .    .


B-ORG  NNP    Minox
O  POS    's
O  NNS    woes
O  VBP    are
O  RB    just
O  NN    part
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    restructuring
O  IN    of
B-LOC  NNP    West
I-LOC  NNP    Germany
O  POS    's
O  JJ    proud
O  NN    camera
O  NN    industry
O  ,    ,
O  WDT    which
O  VBZ    has
O  VBN    seen
O  DT    the
O  RB    only
O  JJ    other
O  CD    two
O  JJ    all-German
O  NNS    companies
O  ,    ,
B-ORG  NNP    Leica
O  CC    and
B-ORG  NNP    Rollei
O  ,    ,
O  VB    drop
O  IN    out
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  JJ    amateur
O  JJ    automatic
O  VBP    focus
O  NN    camera
O  NN    market
O  TO    to
O  VB    concentrate
O  IN    on
O  VBG    producing
O  JJ    high-priced
O  JJ    professional
O  NN    gear
O  .    .


O  DT    The
O  JJ    so-called
O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  NN    spy
O  NN    camera
O  POS    '
O  ''    '
O  VBN    used
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  CD    1963
B-PER  NNP    James
I-PER  NNP    Bond
O  NN    movie
O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  IN    From
O  NNP    Russia
O  IN    With
O  NNP    Love
O  POS    '
O  ''    '
O  MD    can
O  VB    be
O  VBN    concealed
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NN    palm
O  CC    or
O  RB    easily
O  VBD    slipped
O  IN    into
O  DT    a
O  JJ    normal
O  NN    pocket
O  .    .


O  DT    A
O  JJR    newer
O  NN    version
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NNP    Minox
O  NNP    EC
O  ,    ,
O  VBZ    is
O  RB    even
O  JJR    smaller
O  ,    ,
O  IN    about
O  IN    as
O  JJ    long
O  CC    and
O  JJ    thick
O  IN    as
O  DT    a
O  JJ    normal
O  NN    index
O  NN    finger
O  ,    ,
O  CC    and
O  RB    not
O  JJR    more
O  IN    that
O  JJ    two-fingers
O  RB    wide
O  .    .



O  NN    Loss
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NNS    jobs
O  RB    also
O  VBZ    means
O  JJ    small
O  NNS    businesses
O  IN    in
B-LOC  NNP    Heuchelheim
O  MD    will
O  VB    lose
O  DT    the
O  NNS    customers
O  WP    who
O  VBD    used
O  TO    to
O  VB    go
O  NN    shopping
O  RB    there
O  IN    after
O  NN    work
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Marx
O  VBD    said
O  .    .



B-PER  NN    Corduwener
O  RB    immediately
O  VB    cut
O  DT    the
O  NN    workforce
O  TO    to
O  VB    streamline
O  DT    the
O  NN    operation
O  ,    ,
O  CC    but
O  RB    even
O  IN    with
O  NN    $40
O  CD    million
O  IN    in
O  NNS    sales
O  IN    in
O  CD    1988
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    company
O  VBD    lost
O  NN    $3.4
O  CD    million
O  IN    for
O  DT    the
O  NN    year
O  .    .


O  PP$    Its
O  NNS    debts
O  VBD    swelled
O  TO    to
O  NN    $25.7
O  CD    million
O  .    .


O  PRP    They
O  VBD    worked
O  JJ    extra
O  NNS    shifts
O  TO    to
O  VB    fill
O  NN    contract
O  NNS    obligations
O  CC    and
O  VB    keep
O  DT    the
O  NN    firm
O  IN    in
O  NN    operation
O  ,    ,
O  NN    mayor
B-PER  NNP    Marx
O  VBD    said
O  .    .



O  PRP    He
O  VBD    estimated
O  CD    1988
O  NNS    sales
O  IN    at
O  NN    $20
O  CD    million
O  CC    but
O  RB    also
O  VBD    declined
O  TO    to
O  VB    estimate
O  NNS    profits
O  .    .


O  NN    End
O  NNP    Adv
O  NNP    Weekend
O  NNP    Jan.
O  VBD    14-15


O  NN    Money
O  NNPS    Funds
O  NNP    Rose
O  NN    $4.36
O  CD    Billion
O  IN    in
O  JJS    Latest
O  NN    Week
O  TO    to
O  VB    Record
O  NNP    High


B-LOC  NNP    NEW
I-LOC  NNP    YORK
O  -LRB-    -LRB-
B-ORG  NNP    AP
O  -RRB-    -RRB-


O  NNS    Assets
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    nation
O  POS    's
O  CD    453
O  NN    money
O  NN    market
O  JJ    mutual
O  NNS    funds
O  VBD    rose
O  NN    $4.36
O  CD    billion
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  JJS    latest
O  NN    week
O  TO    to
O  DT    an
O  JJ    all-time
O  NN    high
O  IN    of
O  NN    $282.4
O  CD    billion
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
B-ORG  NN    Investment
I-ORG  NNP    Company
I-ORG  NNP    Institute
O  VBD    said
O  NNP    Thursday
O  .    .


O  DT    The
O  NN    rise
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  JJ    seven-day
O  NN    period
O  VBD    ended
O  NNP    Wednesday
O  VBD    followed
O  DT    a
O  NN    $449.5
O  CD    million
O  NN    drop
O  IN    in
O  NN    fund
O  NNS    assets
O  DT    the
O  JJ    previous
O  NN    week
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  JJ    Washington-based
O  JJ    mutual
O  NN    fund
O  NN    trade
O  NN    group
O  VBD    said
O  .    .


O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  IN    In
O  DT    a
O  JJ    sharp
O  NN    reversal
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  JJ    end-of-the-year
O  NN    decline
O  ,    ,
O  NNS    assets
O  IN    of
O  NN    money
O  NN    market
O  NNS    funds
O  VBD    staged
O  DT    an
O  JJ    impressive
O  NN    advance
O  TO    to
O  VB    reach
O  DT    an
O  JJ    all-time
O  JJ    high
O  NN    record
O  ,    ,
O  ''    '
O  ''    '
O  VBD    said
B-PER  NNP    Jacob
I-PER  NNP    Dreyer
O  ,    ,
O  NN    vice
O  CC    and
O  NN    chief
O  NN    economist
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    group
O  .    .


O  DT    The
O  JJ    new
O  NN    record
O  VBZ    eclipses
O  DT    the
O  JJ    previous
O  JJ    all-time
O  NN    high
O  IN    of
O  NN    $281.89
O  CD    billion
O  VBD    reported
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NN    week
O  VBD    ended
O  NNP    Nov.
O  CD    23
O  .    .


O  DT    The
O  JJS    biggest
O  JJ    weekly
O  NN    rise
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NNS    funds
O  POS    '
O  NNS    assets
O  NN    _
O  NN    $9.64
O  CD    billion
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NN    week
O  VBD    ended
O  NNP    Oct.
O  CD    21
O  ,    ,
O  CD    1987
O  NN    _
O  VBD    came
O  IN    during
O  DT    the
O  NN    stock
O  NN    market
O  NN    collapse
O  IN    as
O  NNS    investors
O  VBD    sought
O  JJ    safe
O  NNS    havens
O  IN    for
O  PP$    their
O  NN    money
O  .    .


O  DT    The
B-ORG  NN    Investment
I-ORG  NNP    Company
I-ORG  NNP    Institute
O  VBD    said
O  IN    that
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  JJS    latest
O  NN    week
O  ,    ,
O  NNS    assets
O  IN    of
O  CD    225
O  JJ    general
O  NN    purpose
O  NNS    funds
O  VBD    rose
O  NN    $239.5
O  CD    million
O  TO    to
O  NN    $90.17
O  CD    billion
O  ,    ,
O  NNS    assets
O  IN    of
O  CD    91
O  NN    broker-dealer
O  NNS    funds
O  VBD    rose
O  NN    $3.61
O  CD    billion
O  TO    to
O  NN    $119.28
O  CD    billion
O  ,    ,
O  CC    and
O  NNS    assets
O  IN    of
O  CD    137
O  JJ    institutional
O  NNS    funds
O  VBD    rose
O  NN    $519.2
O  CD    million
O  TO    to
O  NN    $72.94
O  CD    billion
O  .    .



O  DT    The
O  JJ    30-day
O  NN    average
O  NN    yield
O  VBD    rose
O  TO    to
O  CD    8.22
O  NN    percent
O  IN    from
O  CD    8.14
O  NN    percent
O  ,    ,
B-PER  VB    Donoghue
O  POS    's
O  VBD    said
O  .    .


O  DT    The
O  NN    newsletter
O  NNP    Bank
O  NNP    Rate
O  NNP    Monitor
O  VBD    said
O  PP$    its
O  NN    survey
O  IN    of
O  CD    100
O  VBG    leading
O  JJ    commercial
O  NNS    banks
O  ,    ,
O  NNS    savings
O  CC    and
O  NN    loan
O  NNS    assocations
O  CC    and
O  NNS    savings
O  NNS    banks
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NN    nation
O  POS    's
O  CD    10
O  JJS    largest
O  NNS    markets
O  VBD    showed
O  DT    the
O  JJ    effective
O  JJ    annual
O  VBP    yield
O  JJ    available
O  IN    on
O  NN    money
O  NN    market
O  NNS    accounts
O  VBD    rose
O  TO    to
O  CD    6.24
O  NN    percent
O  IN    as
O  IN    of
O  NNP    Wednesday
O  IN    from
O  CD    6.22
O  NN    percent
O  DT    a
O  NN    week
O  RB    earlier
O  .    .


O  DT    The
O  NNP    North
O  NNP    Palm
O  NNP    Beach
O  ,    ,
O  JJ    Fla.-based
O  NN    newsletter
O  VBD    said
O  DT    the
O  JJ    effective
O  JJ    annual
O  VBP    yield
O  JJ    available
O  IN    on
O  JJ    special
O  NNS    savings
O  NNS    accounts
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    called
O  NNP    Super
O  RB    NOW
O  VBZ    accounts
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    rose
O  TO    to
O  CD    5.14
O  NN    percent
O  IN    from
O  CD    5.13
O  NN    percent
O  .    .


O  NNP    Bank
O  NNP    Rate
O  NNP    Monitor
O  VBD    said
O  DT    the
O  JJ    effective
O  JJ    annual
O  NN    yield
O  VBD    was
O  CD    8.26
O  NN    percent
O  IN    on
O  JJ    six-month
O  NNS    certificates
O  IN    of
O  NN    deposit
O  ,    ,
O  IN    up
O  IN    from
O  CD    8.21
O  DT    the
O  JJ    previous
O  NN    week
O  .    .


O  NNS    Yields
O  VBD    were
O  CD    8.51
O  NN    percent
O  IN    on
O  JJ    1-year
O  NNS    CDs
O  ,    ,
O  IN    up
O  IN    from
O  CD    8.48
O  NN    percent
O  :    ;
O  CD    8.63
O  NN    percent
O  IN    on
O  CD    2
O  -LRB-    -LCB-
O  JJ    -year
O  NNS    CDs
O  ,    ,
O  IN    up
O  IN    from
O  CD    8.58
O  NN    percent
O  :    ;
O  CC    and
O  CD    8.75
O  NN    percent
O  IN    on
O  JJ    5-year
O  NNS    CDs
O  ,    ,
O  IN    up
O  IN    from
O  CD    8.71
O  NN    percent
O  .    .


B-LOC  NNP    NEW
I-LOC  NNP    ORLEANS
O  -LRB-    -LRB-
B-ORG  NNP    AP
O  -RRB-    -RRB-


O  NNP    Fried
O  NN    chicken
O  NN    king
B-PER  NNP    Al
I-PER  NNP    Copeland
O  MD    may
O  VB    resume
O  PP$    his
O  NN    $290
O  CD    million
O  NN    takeover
O  NN    attempt
O  IN    against
B-ORG  NNP    Church
I-ORG  POS    's
I-ORG  NNP    Fried
I-ORG  NNP    Chicken
O  ,    ,
O  DT    a
O  JJ    federal
O  NNS    appeals
O  NN    court
O  VBD    ruled
O  NNP    Thursday
O  .    .



O  PRP    They
O  VBD    did
O  RB    not
O  VB    go
O  IN    into
O  PP$    their
O  NNS    reasons
O  IN    for
O  VBG    upholding
O  DT    the
O  NN    ruling
O  VBD    handed
O  IN    down
O  NNP    Nov.
O  CD    28
O  IN    by
O  NNP    U.S.
O  NNP    District
O  NNP    Judge
B-PER  NNP    Charles
I-PER  NNP    Schwartz
O  ,    ,
O  VBG    saying
O  RB    only
O  IN    that
O  PRP    they
O  VBD    affirmed
O  PRP    it
O  IN    on
O  DT    all
O  NNS    points
O  .    .



B-PER  NNP    Struve
O  VBN    argued
O  IN    that
O  DT    the
O  JJ    $8-a-share
O  NN    takeover
O  NN    bid
O  MD    should
O  VB    be
O  VBN    halted
O  IN    because
O  PRP    it
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    based
O  IN    on
O  NN    insider
O  NN    information
O  VBN    provided
O  IN    by
O  DT    a
O  JJ    former
B-ORG  NNP    Church
I-ORG  POS    's
O  NN    executive
O  RB    now
O  VBN    employed
O  IN    by
B-ORG  NNP    Popeyes
O  ,    ,
O  CC    and
O  IN    because
O  VBG    merging
O  DT    the
O  NN    nation
O  POS    's
O  NN    No.
O  CD    2
O  CC    and
O  CD    3
O  JJ    fried
O  NN    chicken
O  NNS    chains
O  MD    would
O  VB    violate
O  JJ    federal
O  JJ    antitrust
O  NNS    laws
O  .    .



O  DT    The
O  NN    chain
O  VBZ    has
O  VBD    said
O  IN    that
O  PRP    it
O  VBZ    owns
O  CD    3.2
O  NN    percent
O  IN    of
B-ORG  NNP    Church
I-ORG  POS    s
O  NN    stock
O  CC    and
O  VBZ    has
O  VBN    been
O  VBN    tendered
O  DT    another
O  CD    14.6
O  CD    million
O  NN    _
O  IN    about
O  CD    40.6
O  NN    percent
O  NN    _
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  CD    35.9
O  CD    million
O  NNS    shares
O  JJ    outstanding
O  .    .


O  IN    By
B-PER  NNP    DAVID
I-PER  NNP    DISHNEAU


O  NN    Copper
O  NNS    futures
O  NNS    prices
O  VBD    surged
O  NNP    Thursday
O  IN    on
B-LOC  NNP    New
I-LOC  NNP    York
I-LOC  POS    's
I-LOC  NNP    Commodity
I-LOC  NNP    Exchange
O  IN    amid
O  NNS    signs
O  IN    of
O  VBG    tightening
O  NNS    supplies
O  CC    and
O  NN    production
O  NNS    problems
O  IN    against
O  DT    a
O  NN    backdrop
O  IN    of
O  JJ    steady
O  NN    demand
O  .    .


O  IN    On
O  JJ    other
O  NNS    markets
O  ,    ,
O  JJ    precious
O  NNS    metals
O  VBD    finished
O  VBN    mixed
O  :    ;
O  NN    coffee
O  NNS    futures
O  VBD    ended
O  JJR    higher
O  :    ;
O  NNS    grains
O  CC    and
O  NNS    soybeans
O  VBD    were
O  VBN    mixed
O  :    ;
O  NN    energy
O  NNS    futures
O  VBD    were
O  RB    mostly
O  JJR    higher
O  :    ;
O  NNS    cattle
O  NNS    futures
O  VBD    were
O  JJR    higher
O  :    ;
O  NN    pork
O  NNS    futures
O  VBD    were
O  VBN    mixed
O  :    ;
O  CC    and
O  NN    stock-index
O  NNS    futures
O  VBD    advanced
O  .    .


O  NNP    Copper
O  VBD    settled
O  CD    0.30
O  NN    cent
O  TO    to
O  CD    4.35
O  NNS    cents
O  JJR    higher
O  IN    with
O  DT    the
O  NN    spot
O  NN    price
O  IN    at
O  NN    $1.489
O  DT    a
O  NN    pound
O  CC    and
O  DT    the
O  RBS    most
O  JJ    active
O  NNS    futures
O  NN    contract
O  ,    ,
O  IN    for
O  NN    delivery
O  IN    in
O  NNP    March
O  ,    ,
O  IN    at
O  NN    $1.379
O  DT    a
O  NN    pound
O  .    .


O  NNS    Analysts
O  VBD    said
O  VBG    buying
O  NN    interest
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    piqued
O  IN    by
O  DT    the
B-ORG  NNP    Commodity
I-ORG  NNP    Exchange
O  POS    's
O  NN    report
O  IN    of
O  DT    a
O  JJ    500-ton
O  VB    decline
O  NNP    Wednesday
O  IN    in
O  NNS    inventories
O  IN    of
O  NN    copper
O  IN    for
O  NN    delivery
O  IN    against
O  NNS    futures
O  NNS    contracts
O  .    .



O  CC    And
O  NN    copper
O  NN    production
O  IN    in
B-LOC  NNP    Zambia
O  CC    and
B-LOC  NNP    Zaire
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    fourth-
O  CC    and
O  JJ    fifth-largest
O  NNS    producers
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    fell
O  IN    by
O  CD    135
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  JJ    metric
O  NNS    tons
O  JJ    last
O  NN    year
O  JJ    due
O  TO    to
O  JJ    mechanical
O  CC    and
O  NN    transportation
O  NNS    difficulties
O  ,    ,
O  PRP    he
O  VBD    said
O  .    .


O  RB    Meanwhile
O  ,    ,
O  NN    copper
O  NN    consumption
O  VBZ    is
O  IN    at
O  PP$    its
O  JJ    seasonal
O  NN    peak
O  ,    ,
O  CC    and
O  NNS    projections
O  IN    for
O  VBD    continued
O  JJ    economic
O  NN    expansion
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    United
I-LOC  NNPS    States
O  ,    ,
B-LOC  NNP    Japan
O  CC    and
B-LOC  NNP    Western
I-LOC  NNP    Europe
O  VBP    suggest
O  IN    that
O  JJ    strong
O  NN    demand
O  IN    for
O  DT    the
O  NN    metal
O  MD    will
O  VB    continue
O  ,    ,
O  NNS    analysts
O  VBD    said
O  .    .



O  NNP    Gold
O  VBD    advanced
O  RB    marginally
O  IN    while
O  NN    silver
O  NNS    futures
O  VBD    fell
O  IN    for
O  DT    the
O  JJ    fourth
O  JJ    straight
O  NN    day
O  IN    on
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    Commodity
I-LOC  NNP    Exchange
O  .    .


O  NNP    Gold
O  VBD    settled
O  CD    50
O  NNS    cents
O  TO    to
O  CD    60
O  NNS    cents
O  RBR    higher
O  IN    with
O  NNP    February
O  IN    at
O  NN    $405.80
O  DT    a
O  NN    troy
O  NN    ounce
O  :    ;
O  NN    silver
O  VBD    was
O  CD    0.5
O  NN    cent
O  TO    to
O  CD    1.5
O  NNS    cents
O  RBR    lower
O  IN    with
O  NNP    March
O  IN    at
O  NN    $5.985
O  DT    a
O  NN    troy
O  NN    ounce
O  .    .


O  NN    Coffee
O  NNS    futures
O  VBD    ended
O  JJR    higher
O  IN    in
O  DT    a
O  NN    day
O  IN    of
O  JJ    volatile
O  NN    trading
O  IN    on
B-LOC  NNP    New
I-LOC  NNP    York
O  POS    's
O  NN    Coffee
O  ,    ,
O  NNP    Sugar
O  NN    &amp
O  ;    ;


O  NNP    Coffee
O  VBD    settled
O  CD    0.5
O  NN    cent
O  TO    to
O  CD    3.3
O  NNS    cents
O  RBR    higher
O  IN    with
O  NNP    March
O  IN    at
O  NN    $1.4211
O  DT    a
O  NN    pound
O  .    .


O  NNP    Grain
O  CC    and
O  NN    soybean
O  NNS    futures
O  VBD    finished
O  VBN    mixed
O  IN    on
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    Chicago
I-LOC  NNP    Board
I-LOC  IN    of
I-LOC  NNP    Trade
O  IN    as
O  NNS    traders
O  VBD    adjusted
O  PP$    their
O  NNS    positions
O  RB    ahead
O  IN    of
O  NNP    Friday
O  POS    's
O  NN    crop
O  NN    report
O  IN    from
O  DT    the
B-ORG  NNP    Agriculture
I-ORG  NNP    Department
O  .    .


O  DT    The
O  NN    crop
O  NN    report
O  ,    ,
O  JJ    due
O  IN    out
O  IN    after
O  NNP    Friday
O  POS    's
O  JJ    close
O  IN    of
O  NN    trading
O  ,    ,
O  RB    also
O  MD    will
O  VB    contain
O  DT    the
O  NNP    USDA
O  POS    's
O  JJ    final
O  CD    1988
O  NN    crop
O  NN    production
O  NNS    totals
O  ,    ,
O  JJ    new
O  NNS    estimates
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    nation
O  POS    's
O  NN    grain
O  CC    and
O  NN    soybean
O  NNS    stockpiles
O  CC    and
O  VBZ    estimates
O  IN    for
O  CD    1989
O  NN    corn
O  CC    and
O  NN    soybean
O  NN    acreage
O  .    .


O  NNP    Wheat
O  VBD    settled
O  CD    3
O  NN    -
O  NNS    cents
O  JJR    lower
O  TO    to
O  -LRB-    -LCB-
O  NN    cent
O  JJR    higher
O  IN    with
O  NNP    March
O  IN    at
O  NN    $4.41
O  NN    -
O  DT    a
O  NN    bushel
O  :    ;
O  NN    corn
O  VBD    was
O  -RRB-    -RCB-
O  NN    cent
O  JJR    lower
O  TO    to
O  CD    1
O  -LRB-    -LCB-
O  NNS    cents
O  JJR    higher
O  IN    with
O  NNP    March
O  IN    at
O  NN    $2.86
O  DT    a
O  NN    bushel
O  :    ;
O  NNS    oats
O  VBD    were
O  -LRB-    -LCB-
O  NN    cent
O  JJR    lower
O  TO    to
O  CD    1
O  -RRB-    -RCB-
O  NNS    cents
O  JJR    higher
O  IN    with
O  NNP    March
O  IN    at
O  NN    $2.37
O  -RRB-    -RCB-
O  DT    a
O  NN    bushel
O  :    ;
O  NNS    soybeans
O  VBD    were
O  CD    2
O  -LRB-    -LCB-
O  NNS    cents
O  JJR    lower
O  TO    to
O  CD    1
O  NN    -
O  NNS    cents
O  JJR    higher
O  IN    with
O  NNP    January
O  IN    at
O  NN    $7.98
O  -LRB-    -LCB-
O  DT    a
O  NN    bushel
O  .    .


O  JJS    Most
O  NN    energy
O  NNS    futures
O  NNS    prices
O  VBD    finished
O  RB    moderately
O  JJR    higher
O  IN    on
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    New
I-LOC  NNP    York
I-LOC  NNP    Mercantile
I-LOC  NNP    Exchange
O  IN    after
O  VBG    falling
O  RB    earlier
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NN    day
O  .    .


O  NNP    West
O  NNP    Texas
O  NNP    Intermediate
O  JJ    crude
O  NN    oil
O  VBD    settled
O  CD    3
O  NNS    cents
O  TO    to
O  CD    18
O  NNS    cents
O  RBR    higher
O  IN    with
O  NNP    February
O  IN    at
O  NN    $18.17
O  DT    a
O  NN    barrel
O  :    ;
O  NN    heating
O  NN    oil
O  VBD    was
O  CD    .85
O  NN    cent
O  JJR    lower
O  TO    to
O  CD    .30
O  NN    cent
O  JJR    higher
O  IN    with
O  NNP    February
O  IN    at
O  CD    52.84
O  NNS    cents
O  DT    a
O  NN    gallon
O  :    ;
O  JJ    unleaded
O  NN    gasoline
O  VBD    was
O  CD    .50
O  NN    cent
O  TO    to
O  CD    .74
O  NN    cent
O  JJR    higher
O  IN    with
O  NNP    February
O  IN    at
O  CD    49.27
O  NNS    cents
O  DT    a
O  NN    gallon
O  .    .


O  IN    On
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    Chicago
I-LOC  NNP    Mercantile
I-LOC  NNP    Exchange
O  ,    ,
O  JJ    live
O  NNS    cattle
O  VBD    settled
O  CD    .10
O  NN    cent
O  TO    to
O  CD    .22
O  NN    cent
O  JJR    higher
O  IN    with
O  NNP    February
O  IN    at
O  CD    74.02
O  NNS    cents
O  DT    a
O  NN    pound
O  :    ;
O  NN    feeder
O  NNS    cattle
O  VBD    were
O  JJ    unchanged
O  TO    to
O  CD    .40
O  NN    cent
O  JJR    higher
O  IN    with
O  NNP    January
O  IN    at
O  CD    85.05
O  NNS    cents
O  DT    a
O  NN    pound
O  :    ;
O  JJ    live
O  NNS    hogs
O  VBD    were
O  CD    .20
O  NN    cent
O  JJR    lower
O  TO    to
O  CD    .30
O  NN    cent
O  JJR    higher
O  IN    with
O  NNP    February
O  IN    at
O  CD    45.57
O  NNS    cents
O  DT    a
O  NN    pound
O  :    ;
O  VBN    frozen
O  NN    pork
O  NNS    bellies
O  VBD    were
O  CD    .47
O  NN    cent
O  TO    to
O  CD    .87
O  NN    cent
O  JJR    higher
O  IN    with
O  NNP    February
O  IN    at
O  CD    42.70
O  NNS    cents
O  DT    a
O  NN    pound
O  .    .


O  NN    Stock-index
O  NNS    futures
O  VBD    advanced
O  RB    modestly
O  IN    on
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    Chicago
I-LOC  NNP    Mercantile
I-LOC  NNP    Exchange
O  ,    ,
O  WRB    where
O  DT    the
O  NN    contract
O  IN    for
O  NNP    March
O  NN    delivery
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NNP    Standard
O  NN    &amp
O  :    ;


O  NNP    Poor
O  POS    's
O  CD    500
O  NN    index
O  VBD    settled
O  CD    .85
O  NN    point
O  JJR    higher
O  IN    at
O  CD    285.25
O  .    .


O  DT    Each
O  NN    point
O  VBZ    is
O  NN    worth
O  NN    $500
O  .    .


O  IN    By
B-PER  NNP    JAMES
I-PER  NNP    O.
I-PER  NNP    CLIFFORD


B-ORG  NNP    Associated
I-ORG  NNP    Press
O  NNP    Writer


B-LOC  NNP    SAN
O  -LRB-    -LRB-
B-ORG  NNP    AP
O  -RRB-    -RRB-


O  DT    A
O  JJ    congressional
O  NN    hearing
O  VBD    convened
O  TO    to
O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  VB    clean
O  IN    up
O  DT    the
O  NN    mess
O  ''    '
O  ''    '
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NN    nation
O  POS    's
O  NNS    savings
O  CC    and
O  NNS    loans
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    told
O  NNP    Thursday
O  IN    that
O  RBR    more
O  IN    than
O  NN    $220
O  CD    million
O  IN    in
O  NNS    losses
O  IN    from
O  NN    insider
O  NN    fraud
O  VBP    have
O  VBN    been
O  VBN    uncovered
O  IN    in
O  NNS    thrifts
O  IN    in
B-LOC  NNP    California
O  ,    ,
B-LOC  NNP    Nevada
O  CC    and
B-LOC  NNP    Arizona
O  .    .



B-PER  NNP    Cirona
O  ,    ,
O  WP$    whose
O  NN    jurisdiction
O  VBZ    includes
O  DT    the
O  CD    three
O  NNS    states
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    testified
O  IN    before
O  DT    the
B-ORG  NNP    House
I-ORG  NNP    Banking
I-ORG  ,    ,
I-ORG  NNP    Finance
I-ORG  CC    and
I-ORG  NNP    Urban
I-ORG  NNP    Affairs
I-ORG  NNP    Committee
O  .    .


B-PER  NNP    Cirona
O  VBD    said
O  IN    that
O  IN    since
O  NNP    August
O  IN    of
O  CD    1987
O  PP$    his
O  NNS    investigators
O  VBD    had
O  VBN    referred
O  CD    5
O  ,    ,
O  CD    384
O  NNS    cases
O  IN    of
O  JJ    possible
O  NN    fraud
O  CC    or
O  NN    abuse
O  TO    to
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    U.S.
O  NN    attorney
O  POS    's
O  NN    office
O  .    .


O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  IN    For
O  DT    this
O  NN    reason
O  PRP    we
O  VBP    have
O  VBN    established
O  DT    a
O  JJ    special
O  NN    system
O  IN    of
O  ``    `
O  NN    priority
O  NNS    referrals
O  POS    '
O  DT    that
O  VBZ    involves
O  NNS    insiders
O  CC    or
O  NNS    amounts
O  IN    in
O  NN    excess
O  IN    of
O  NN    $100
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  .    .


O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  PRP    We
O  VBP    estimate
O  IN    that
O  NNS    losses
O  TO    to
B-LOC  JJ    11th
I-LOC  NNP    District
O  NNS    institutions
O  IN    on
O  DT    these
O  NN    priority
O  NNS    referrals
O  ,    ,
O  IN    as
O  IN    of
O  NNP    September
O  CD    23
O  ,    ,
O  CD    1988
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    amounted
O  TO    to
O  IN    over
O  NN    $220
O  NN    million.
O  ''    '
O  ''    '


O  NNP    Committee
O  NNP    Chairman
B-PER  NNP    Henry
I-PER  NNP    Gonzalez
O  ,    ,
O  NNP    D-Texas
O  ,    ,
O  VBN    called
O  IN    for
O  DT    a
O  JJ    full
O  NN    analysis
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    crisis
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NNS    savings
O  CC    and
O  NNS    loans
O  NN    industry
O  ,    ,
O  IN    in
O  WDT    which
O  NN    government
O  NNS    bailouts
O  VBD    exceeded
O  NN    $38
O  CD    billion
O  IN    in
O  CD    1988
O  .    .


O  NNS    Estimates
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    cost
O  TO    to
O  VB    rescue
O  DT    the
O  VBG    remaining
O  CD    350
O  CC    or
O  RB    so
O  JJ    involvent
O  NNS    thrifts
O  VBP    have
O  VBN    ranged
O  IN    from
O  NN    $50
O  CD    billion
O  TO    to
O  NN    $75
O  CD    billion
O  .    .



O  DT    The
O  NN    appointment
O  VBZ    is
O  VBN    effective
O  NNP    April
O  CD    1
O  .    .


O  JJ    Last
O  NNP    April
O  ,    ,
B-ORG  NNP    Knight-Ridder
O  POS    's
O  NN    board
O  IN    of
O  NNS    directors
O  VBD    authorized
O  DT    the
O  NN    repurchase
O  IN    of
O  CD    5
O  CD    million
O  NNS    shares
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    company
O  POS    's
O  NN    stock
O  .    .


O  IN    At
O  PP$    its
O  NNP    December
O  NN    meeting
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    board
O  VBD    authorized
O  DT    the
O  NN    repurchase
O  IN    of
O  DT    an
O  JJ    additional
O  CD    5
O  CD    million
O  NNS    shares
O  .    .


O  IN    For
O  NNP    Release
O  NNP    Weekend
O  NNP    Editions
O  NNP    Jan.
O  CD    14-15
O  CC    and
O  RB    Thereafter


O  NNP    LaserPhoto
O  NNP    AB1
O  IN    of
O  NNP    Jan.
O  CD    10


O  IN    By
B-PER  NNP    LESLIE
I-PER  NNP    ZGANJAR


B-ORG  NNP    Associated
I-ORG  NNP    Press
O  NNP    Writer


B-LOC  NNP    MIDDLETOWN
O  ,    ,
B-LOC  NNP    N.Y
I-LOC  .    .


O  DT    A
O  JJ    foul
O  NN    smell
O  VBZ    permeates
O  DT    the
O  NNS    warehouses
O  WRB    where
O  NNS    bundles
O  IN    of
O  VBN    used
O  JJ    plastic
O  NN    milk
O  NNS    jugs
O  CC    and
O  NN    laundry
O  NN    detergent
O  NNS    bottles
O  VBP    are
O  VBN    stacked
O  TO    to
O  DT    the
O  NN    ceiling
O  .    .


O  CC    But
O  TO    to
B-ORG  NNP    Eaglebrook
I-ORG  NNS    Plastics
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    odor
O  VBZ    is
O  DT    the
O  JJ    sweet
O  NN    smell
O  IN    of
O  NN    success
O  .    .



O  DT    The
O  NN    plant
O  VBZ    pays
O  NN    $100
O  TO    to
O  NN    $150
O  IN    per
O  NN    ton
O  IN    of
O  VBN    used
O  NN    plastic
O  ,    ,
O  VBG    depending
O  IN    on
O  WRB    how
O  JJ    clean
O  CC    and
O  VBN    sorted
O  PRP    it
O  VBZ    is
O  .    .



O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  IN    That
O  VBZ    's
O  DT    a
O  NN    lot
O  IN    of
O  NN    work
O  IN    for
O  DT    a
O  NN    person
O  ,    ,
O  CC    and
O  IN    so
O  IN    about
O  CD    98
O  NN    percent
O  IN    of
O  DT    those
O  VBN    used
O  NNS    containers
O  VBD    ended
O  IN    up
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NN    landfill
O  .    .


O  DT    The
O  NN    company
O  VBD    developed
O  WP    what
O  PRP    it
O  RB    affectionately
O  VBZ    calls
O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  NNP    Mr.
O  NNP    Clean
O  ,    ,
O  ''    '
O  ''    '
O  DT    a
O  NN    $200
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  NN    machine
O  IN    that
O  NN    scrubs
O  NNS    labels
O  CC    and
O  NNS    bits
O  IN    of
O  NN    food
O  IN    from
O  DT    the
O  NN    once-smelly
O  VBZ    empties
O  .    .


B-ORG  NNP    Eaglebrook
O  VBD    opened
O  NN    shop
O  IN    in
B-LOC  NNP    Chicago
O  IN    about
O  CD    five
O  NNS    years
O  IN    ago
O  IN    with
O  NN    $10
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  CC    and
O  DT    an
O  VBG    answering
O  NN    machine
O  .    .


O  PRP    It
O  RB    now
O  VBZ    has
O  JJ    annual
O  NNS    sales
O  IN    of
O  NN    $5
O  CD    million
O  CC    and
O  CD    50
O  NNS    employees
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Stephens
O  VBD    said
O  .    .


O  RB    Once
O  DT    the
O  NN    business
O  VBD    took
O  VB    hold
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    Midwest
O  ,    ,
B-ORG  NNP    Eaglebrook
O  NNS    officials
O  VBD    decided
O  DT    the
O  NN    company
O  VBD    needed
O  DT    an
B-LOC  NNP    East
I-LOC  NNP    Coast
O  NN    location
O  .    .



B-ORG  NNP    Eaglebrook
I-ORG  NNP    East
O  VBD    opened
O  IN    in
B-LOC  NNP    Middletown
O  IN    in
O  NNP    April
O  .    .


O  PRP    It
O  VBZ    expects
O  TO    to
O  VB    post
O  NN    $2.5
O  CD    million
O  IN    in
O  NNS    sales
O  IN    for
O  CD    1988
O  .    .


O  IN    About
O  CD    2.2
O  CD    billion
O  NNS    pounds
O  IN    of
O  JJ    high-density
O  NN    polyethylene
O  NN    plastic
O  NNS    containers
O  VBP    are
O  VBN    produced
O  DT    each
O  NN    year
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    United
I-LOC  NNPS    States
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    company
O  VBD    said
O  .    .


B-ORG  NN    Eaglebrook
I-ORG  NNS    Plastics
O  VBZ    says
O  PRP    it
O  MD    will
O  VB    recover
O  JJR    more
O  IN    than
O  CD    3
O  CD    million
O  NNS    pounds
O  IN    of
O  DT    that
O  .    .



O  IN    In
O  NN    fact
O  ,    ,
O  RB    only
O  IN    about
O  CD    20
O  NN    percent
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  JJ    first
O  CD    250
O  NNS    tons
O  IN    of
O  NN    plastic
O  DT    the
O  NN    company
O  VBN    received
O  VBD    fell
O  IN    into
O  DT    the
O  NN    post-consumer
O  NN    category
O  .    .


O  JJ    Plastic
O  IN    from
O  VBN    used
O  NN    milk
O  NNS    jugs
O  ,    ,
O  WDT    which
O  VBZ    is
O  VBN    dyed
O  NNS    shades
O  IN    of
O  JJ    brown
O  CC    and
O  NN    rust
O  ,    ,
O  VBZ    is
O  VBG    being
O  VBN    formed
O  IN    into
O  NNS    shapes
O  WDT    that
O  VBP    resemble
O  JJ    wooden
O  NNS    planks
O  CC    and
O  VBD    sold
O  IN    for
O  NN    building
O  NNS    decks
O  .    .


B-ORG  NN    Eaglebrook
O  VBZ    is
O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  RB    probably
O  DT    the
O  JJS    largest
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  JJ    proprietary
O  NNS    recyclers
O  ,    ,
O  ''    '
O  ''    '
O  VBD    said
B-PER  NNP    Susan
I-PER  NNP    Vadney
O  ,    ,
O  DT    a
O  NN    spokeswoman
O  IN    for
O  DT    the
O  NNP    Journal
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    Society
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NNS    Plastics
O  NN    Industry
O  .    .


O  NN    End
O  NNP    Adv
O  NNP    Weekend
O  NNP    Editions
O  NNP    Jan.
O  VBD    14-15


O  DT    The
O  NN    feature
O  NN    race
O  IN    at
B-LOC  NNP    Mehama
O  POS    's
O  NN    summer
O  JJS    fest
O  NN    wasn
O  NN    't
O  RB    exactly
O  DT    a
O  NN    display
O  IN    of
O  VBG    blazing
O  NN    speed
O  ,    ,
O  CC    but
O  PRP    they
O  NN    didn
O  NN    't
O  VB    call
O  PRP    it
O  DT    the
O  NNP    Slug
O  CC    and
O  NNP    Scotch
O  NNP    Broom
O  NNP    Festival
O  IN    for
O  NN    nothing.



B-PER  NNP    Rick
I-PER  NNP    Urquhart
O  ,    ,
O  NN    father
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  VBG    winning
O  NN    slug
O  NN    trainer
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    said
O  PRP    he
O  VBD    found
O  DT    the
O  NN    racer
O  IN    at
O  DT    a
O  NN    state
O  NN    park.


O  DT    The
O  NN    festival
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    town
O  POS    's
O  JJ    first
O  IN    in
O  CD    30
O  NNS    years
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    was
O  DT    the
O  NN    brainchild
O  IN    of
O  NNS    businessmen
B-PER  NNP    Mike
I-PER  NNP    Boyles
O  CC    and
B-PER  NNP    Bill
I-PER  NNP    Mercer
O  ,    ,
O  WP    who
O  VBD    came
O  IN    up
O  IN    with
O  DT    the
O  NN    idea
O  IN    over
O  DT    a
O  NN    drink
O  IN    at
B-LOC  NNP    Mercer
I-LOC  POS    's
I-LOC  NNP    Fish
I-LOC  NNP    Hatchery
I-LOC  NNP    Tavern.


B-LOC  NNP    EAST
I-LOC  NNP    LANSING
O  ,    ,
B-LOC  NNP    Mich.


O  IN    With
O  CD    2
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  NNS    begonias
O  VBG    blooming
O  IN    on
O  PP$    his
O  NN    chest
O  ,    ,
O  NN    head
O  CC    and
O  NN    tail
O  ,    ,
O  PRP    he
O  VBZ    has
O  VBN    drawn
O  DT    some
O  VBN    surprised
O  VBZ    looks
O  IN    at
B-ORG  NNP    Michigan
I-ORG  NNP    State
I-ORG  NNP    University
O  POS    's
O  JJ    new
B-LOC  NNP    Horticulture
I-LOC  NNP    Demonstration
I-LOC  NNP    Gardens.


O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  WRB    When
O  PRP    I
O  RB    first
O  VBD    saw
O  PRP    it
O  ,    ,
O  PRP    I
O  VBD    thought
O  PRP    it
O  VBD    was
O  DT    a
O  NN    dinosaur
O  ,    ,
O  ''    '
O  ''    '
O  VBD    said
B-PER  NNP    Bobbie
I-PER  NNP    Haskell
O  ,    ,
O  WP    who
O  VBD    came
O  IN    for
O  DT    an
O  NN    evening
O  VBP    walk
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NNS    gardens
O  IN    over
O  DT    the
O  NN    weekend.



O  WRB    When
O  VBN    finished
O  IN    in
O  CD    1993
O  ,    ,
O  NNS    flowers
O  MD    will
O  NN    bloom
O  IN    over
O  CD    7
O  -LRB-    -LCB-
O  NNS    acres
O  CC    and
O  NNP    Wilbir
O  MD    will
O  VB    be
O  DT    the
O  NN    centerpiece
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    garden
O  POS    's
O  NN    circular
O  NN    entrance
O  NN    pavilion.


O  NNP    Text
O  IN    of
O  NNP    Communique
O  NNP    Announcing
B-PER  NNP    Higgins
O  NNP    Execution


B-LOC  NNP    BEIRUT
O  ,    ,
B-LOC  NNP    Lebanon
O  -LRB-    -LRB-
B-ORG  NNP    AP
O  -RRB-    -RRB-



O  PRP    It
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    translated
O  IN    from
O  NNP    Arabic
O  IN    by
B-ORG  DT    The
I-ORG  NNP    Associated
I-ORG  NNP    Press
O  NN    bureau
O  IN    in
B-LOC  NNP    Beirut
O  :    :



O  PRP    We
O  RB    also
O  VB    renew
O  PP$    our
O  NN    stance
O  IN    that
O  DT    the
O  JJ    virtuous
O  NN    sheik
O  CC    and
O  PP$    his
O  CD    two
O  NNS    brethren
O  VB    be
O  RB    immediately
O  VBN    released
O  IN    because
O  WP    what
O  VBZ    is
O  VBG    coming
O  VBZ    is
O  JJR    greater
O  CC    and
B-LOC  NNP    America
O  CC    and
B-LOC  NNP    Israel
O  MD    will
O  VB    bear
O  JJ    full
O  NN    responsibility
O  IN    for
O  NN    it.


O  NN    Death
O  TO    to
B-LOC  NNP    America
O  CC    and
B-LOC  NNP    Israel
O  CC    and
O  DT    the
O  JJ    arrogant
O  CC    and
O  PP$    their
O  NN    agents.


O  PRP    We
O  NN    pledge
O  TO    to
O  PRP    them
O  IN    that
O  PRP    we
O  MD    shall
O  VB    continue
O  PP$    our
O  NN    struggle
O  IN    on
O  DT    the
O  NN    path
O  VBN    drawn
O  IN    by
O  PP$    their
O  VBN    blessed
O  NNS    arms
O  CC    and
O  NN    blood
O  TO    to
O  VB    uproot
O  DT    the
O  JJ    cancerous
B-LOC  NNP    Israel
O  IN    from
O  NN    existence
O  CC    and
O  VB    chop
O  IN    off
O  DT    the
O  NNS    hands
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  JJ    arrogant
O  VBG    toying
O  IN    with
O  PP$    our
O  NN    country
O  CC    and
O  VBN    headed
O  IN    by
O  JJ    criminal
B-LOC  NNP    America
O  ,    ,
O  CC    and
O  TO    to
O  VBP    glorify
O  DT    the
O  JJ    Moslem
O  NN    faith
O  CC    and
O  DT    the
O  NN    nation
O  IN    of
O  NNP    Mohammed
O  NN    til
O  DT    the
O  NN    flag
O  IN    of
O  JJ    Islamic
O  NN    unification
O  VBZ    flutters
O  DT    all
O  IN    over
O  DT    the
O  NN    world.



O  IN    By
B-PER  NNP    RICHARD
I-PER  NNP    COLE


B-ORG  NNP    Associated
I-ORG  NNP    Press
O  NNP    Writer


O  NNP    Chantal
O  VBD    became
O  DT    the
O  JJ    first
O  NN    hurricane
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  JJ    Atlantic
O  NN    season
O  NNP    Monday
O  IN    as
O  PRP    it
O  VBD    bore
O  IN    down
O  IN    on
B-LOC  NNP    Texas
O  CC    and
B-LOC  NNP    Louisiana
O  ,    ,
O  VBG    thwarting
O  NNS    efforts
O  TO    to
O  VB    rescue
O  DT    the
O  NN    crew
O  IN    of
O  DT    a
O  JJ    capsized
O  NN    oil
O  NN    rig
O  CC    and
O  VBG    forcing
O  NN    evacuation
O  IN    of
O  DT    a
O  JJ    coastal
O  NN    island.


O  PRP    It
O  VBD    had
O  DT    a
O  NN    maximum
O  VBD    sustained
O  VBP    wind
O  NN    speed
O  IN    of
O  CD    65
O  NN    mph
O  IN    in
O  JJ    early
O  NN    afternoon
O  CC    and
O  VBD    increased
O  TO    to
O  CD    75
O  NN    mph
O  ,    ,
O  CD    1
O  NN    mph
O  IN    over
O  DT    the
O  NN    threshold
O  IN    for
O  VBG    reclassifying
O  DT    a
O  JJ    tropical
O  VBP    storm
O  DT    a
O  NN    hurricane
O  ,    ,
O  IN    by
O  CD    6
O  NN    p.m.
O  NNP    EDT.



O  VBG    According
O  TO    to
O  DT    the
O  NN    hurricane
O  NN    center
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    hurricane
O  POS    's
O  NN    center
O  POS    's
O  JJS    likeliest
O  NN    landfall
O  MD    would
O  VB    be
O  IN    at
O  CD    7
O  NN    p.m.



O  NNS    Forecasters
O  VBD    said
O  EX    there
O  VBD    was
O  DT    a
O  CD    53
O  NN    percent
O  NN    chance
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    storm
O  VBG    centering
O  IN    on
B-LOC  NNP    Port
I-LOC  NNP    Arthur
O  CC    and
O  DT    a
O  CD    52
O  NN    percent
O  NN    chance
O  IN    of
O  VBG    centering
O  IN    on
B-LOC  NNP    Galveston.


O  NNS    Squalls
O  IN    on
O  DT    the
O  NN    edge
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    storm
O  VBD    dumped
O  JJ    heavy
O  NN    rain
O  IN    on
B-LOC  NNP    New
I-LOC  NNP    Orleans
O  CC    and
O  VBN    forced
O  NN    closure
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  JJ    24-mile
O  JJ    long
O  NN    causeway
O  IN    across
B-LOC  NNP    Lake
I-LOC  NNP    Pontchartrain.



O  NNP    Mayor
B-PER  NNP    Andy
I-PER  NNP    Valence
O  VBD    said
O  PRP    he
O  VBD    feared
O  NNP    Louisiana
O  NNP    Highway
O  CD    1
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  JJ    only
O  VBP    route
O  IN    off
O  DT    the
O  NN    island
O  ,    ,
O  MD    would
O  NN    flood.



O  CD    Two
O  NN    emergency
O  NNS    shelters
O  VBD    opened
O  IN    in
O  JJ    nearby
B-LOC  NNP    Lake
I-LOC  NNP    Charles
O  ,    ,
O  IN    with
O  CD    67
B-LOC  NNP    Cameron
O  NNS    residents
O  VBG    staying
O  IN    in
O  CD    one
O  NN    shelter.



B-PER  NNP    Lutie
I-PER  NNP    Dyson
O  ,    ,
O  CD    62
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    said
O  PRP    she
O  CC    and
O  PP$    her
O  NN    husband
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Clarence
O  ,    ,
O  CD    73
O  ,    ,
O  DT    a
O  VBN    retired
O  JJ    commercial
O  NN    fisherman
O  ,    ,
O  VB    have
O  RB    frequently
O  VBN    evacuated
O  PP$    their
O  NNS    homes
O  IN    since
O  NNP    June
O  CD    1967
O  ,    ,
O  WRB    when
O  NNP    Hurricane
O  NNP    Audrey
O  VBD    slammed
O  RB    ashore
O  CC    and
O  VBD    killed
O  CD    526
O  NNS    people
O  ,    ,
O  VBD    injured
O  RB    nearly
O  CD    4
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  ,    ,
O  VBN    destroyed
O  CC    or
O  VBN    damaged
O  RBR    more
O  IN    than
O  CD    2
O  ,    ,
O  CD    500
O  NNS    homes
O  CC    and
O  VBN    left
O  NNS    millions
O  IN    of
O  NNS    dollars
O  IN    in
O  NN    damage.


O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  PRP    I
O  MD    can
O  NN    't
O  VB    tell
O  PRP    you
O  RB    exactly
O  ,    ,
O  RB    maybe
O  CD    10
O  CC    or
O  CD    12
O  NNS    times
O  IN    since
O  NNP    Audrey
O  ,    ,
O  ''    '
O  ''    '
O  VBD    said
B-PER  NNP    Mrs.
I-PER  NNP    Dyson
O  ,    ,
O  DT    a
O  NN    mother
O  IN    of
O  CD    15
O  WP    who
O  VBD    lost
O  PP$    her
O  NN    home
O  TO    to
O  NNP    Audrey.


O  VBN    Told
O  NN    landfall
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    expected
O  IN    near
B-LOC  NNP    Port
I-LOC  NNP    Arthur
O  ,    ,
B-PER  NNP    Mrs.
I-PER  NNP    Dyson
O  VBD    replied
O  :    :
O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  PRP    They
O  VBD    told
O  PRP    us
O  IN    that
O  IN    for
O  NNP    Audrey
O  ,    ,
O  RB    too
O  ,    ,
O  CC    and
O  PRP    we
O  VBD    got
O  NNP    Audrey.


O  JJ    Heavy
O  NN    weather
O  IN    on
O  DT    the
O  NN    storm
O  POS    's
O  NN    fringe
O  VBD    halted
O  DT    the
O  NN    search
O  IN    for
O  CD    10
O  NNS    men
O  VBD    lost
O  WRB    when
O  DT    an
O  NN    oil
O  VBP    rig
O  VBN    capsized
O  IN    while
O  VBG    being
O  VBN    moved
O  JJ    south
O  IN    of
B-LOC  NNP    Morgan
I-LOC  NNP    City.


O  DT    The
B-ORG  NNP    Coast
I-ORG  NNP    Guard
O  VBD    flew
O  NNS    divers
O  TO    to
O  DT    the
O  NN    rig
O  IN    despite
O  JJ    12-foot
O  NNS    seas
O  CC    and
O  NN    60-mph
O  NN    winds.


O  CD    One
O  NN    man
O  VBD    died
O  IN    after
O  VBG    falling
O  IN    from
O  DT    a
O  NNP    Chevron
O  NN    platform
O  NN    south
O  IN    of
B-LOC  NNP    New
I-LOC  NNP    Orleans.


O  IN    At
O  NN    midnight
O  NNP    EDT
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    hurricane
O  POS    's
O  NN    center
O  VBD    was
O  IN    near
O  NN    latitude
O  CD    28.1
O  NN    north
O  CC    and
O  NN    longitude
O  CD    93.1
O  JJ    west
O  ,    ,
O  CC    or
O  IN    about
O  CD    130
O  NNS    miles
O  RB    southeast
O  IN    of
B-LOC  NNP    Galveston.


O  PRP    It
O  VBD    was
O  VBG    moving
O  NN    north-northwest
O  IN    at
O  CD    10
O  NN    mph
O  CC    and
O  NNS    forecasters
O  VBD    expected
O  PRP    it
O  TO    to
O  VB    continue
O  TO    to
O  VB    gain
O  NN    strength
O  CC    and
O  VB    follow
O  IN    that
O  RB    northwesterly
O  NN    path
O  IN    into
O  NN    midday
O  NNP    Tuesday.


O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  DT    This
O  MD    should
O  VB    bring
O  DT    the
O  NN    center
O  IN    over
O  DT    the
O  JJ    upper
B-LOC  NNP    Texas
O  CC    or
O  JJ    western
B-LOC  NNP    Louisiana
O  NN    coast
O  NN    tomorrow
O  NN    afternoon
O  CC    or
O  NN    evening
O  ,    ,
O  ''    '
O  ''    '
O  VBD    said
B-PER  NNP    Bob
I-PER  NNP    Sheets
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    hurricane
O  NN    center
O  POS    's
O  NN    director.


B-PER  NNS    Sheets
O  VBD    said
O  JJ    tropical
O  NN    storm
O  NN    force
O  NN    wind
O  VBD    extended
O  RB    outward
O  CD    150
O  NNS    miles
O  TO    to
O  DT    the
O  NN    north
O  CC    and
O  CD    125
O  NNS    miles
O  TO    to
O  DT    the
O  NN    south
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  NN    center.


O  DT    A
O  JJ    few
O  NNS    tornadoes
O  VBD    were
O  RB    also
O  RB    likely
O  IN    over
O  NNS    sections
O  IN    of
B-LOC  NNP    Louisiana
O  CC    and
O  JJ    extreme
O  JJ    eastern
B-LOC  NNP    Texas
O  IN    during
O  DT    the
O  NN    night
O  CC    and
O  NNP    Tuesday
O  ,    ,
O  PRP    he
O  NN    said.



O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  PRP    We
O  VBP    're
O  VBG    planning
O  IN    for
O  DT    the
O  JJS    worst
O  CC    and
O  VBG    hoping
O  IN    for
O  DT    the
O  JJS    best
O  ,    ,
O  ''    '
O  ''    '
O  VBD    said
B-PER  NNP    Doug
I-PER  NNP    Matthews
O  ,    ,
O  NN    city
O  NN    manager
O  IN    of
B-LOC  NNP    Galveston
O  ,    ,
O  DT    an
O  NN    island
O  NN    city
O  IN    of
O  CD    60
O  ,    ,
O  CD    000
O  RB    just
O  RB    south
O  IN    of
B-LOC  NNP    Houston.



O  RB    Meanwhile
O  ,    ,
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  JJ    open
B-LOC  JJ    Atlantic
O  ,    ,
O  JJ    tropical
O  NN    depression
O  NN    No.
O  CD    5
O  VBD    had
O  VBN    become
O  NNP    Tropical
O  NN    Storm
O  NNP    Dean
O  IN    by
O  CD    11
O  NN    p.m.
O  NNP    EDT.


O  PRP    It
O  VBD    had
O  VBP    top
O  VBN    sustained
O  NNS    winds
O  IN    of
O  CD    40
O  NN    mph
O  CC    and
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    centered
O  IN    near
O  NN    latitude
O  CD    15.5
O  NN    north
O  CC    and
O  NN    longitude
O  CD    47.8
O  JJ    west
O  ,    ,
O  CC    or
O  IN    about
O  CD    850
O  NNS    miles
O  RB    east
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    Lesser
I-LOC  NNP    Antilles.


O  PRP    It
O  VBD    was
O  VBG    moving
O  RB    west
O  IN    at
O  IN    about
O  CD    15
O  NN    mph
O  ,    ,
O  CC    and
O  VBD    was
O  VBN    expected
O  TO    to
O  VB    gain
O  NN    strength
O  CC    but
O  VB    hold
O  PP$    its
O  NN    course
O  ,    ,
O  NNS    forecasters
O  NN    said.


O  CD    Two
O  JJ    other
O  NNS    depressions
O  VBP    have
O  VBN    formed
O  IN    into
O  VBN    named
O  NNS    storms
O  IN    since
O  DT    the
O  CD    1989
O  JJ    Atlantic
O  NN    hurricane
O  NN    season
O  VBD    began
O  NNP    June
O  NN    1.


O  IN    By
B-PER  NNP    BRYNA
I-PER  NNP    BRENNAN


B-ORG  NNP    Associated
I-ORG  NNP    Press
O  NNP    Writer


O  DT    The
B-ORG  NNP    Agriculture
I-ORG  NNP    Department
O  POS    's
O  JJ    monthly
O  NN    index
O  VBZ    shows
O  NNS    prices
O  NNS    farmers
O  VBD    received
O  IN    for
O  JJ    raw
O  NNS    products
O  VBD    dropped
O  CD    0.7
O  NN    percent
O  IN    in
O  NNP    July
O  IN    from
O  DT    a
O  NN    month
O  RBR    earlier
O  ,    ,
O  CC    but
O  VBD    were
O  IN    up
O  CD    2.8
O  NN    percent
O  IN    from
O  DT    a
O  NN    year
O  NN    ago.


O  DT    The
O  NN    department
O  POS    's
B-ORG  NNP    Agricultural
I-ORG  NNP    Statistics
I-ORG  NNP    Board
O  VBD    said
O  IN    in
O  PP$    its
O  JJ    preliminary
O  NN    report
O  NNP    Monday
O  IN    that
O  VBG    declining
O  NNS    prices
O  IN    for
O  NNS    oranges
O  ,    ,
O  NNS    broilers
O  ,    ,
O  NNS    soybeans
O  CC    and
O  NN    corn
O  VBD    were
O  RB    partially
O  VBN    offset
O  IN    by
O  JJR    higher
O  NNS    prices
O  IN    for
O  NNS    potatoes
O  ,    ,
O  NN    cotton
O  ,    ,
O  NNS    tomatoes
O  CC    and
O  NN    hogs.


O  DT    The
O  NNP    July
O  NN    index
O  IN    of
O  NNS    prices
O  VBN    paid
O  IN    for
O  NNS    commodities
O  CC    and
O  NNS    services
O  ,    ,
O  NN    interest
O  ,    ,
O  NNS    taxes
O  CC    and
O  VB    farm
O  NN    wage
O  NNS    rates
O  VBD    was
O  CD    178
O  NN    percent
O  IN    of
O  PP$    its
O  CD    1977
O  NN    average.


O  DT    The
O  NN    index
O  VBD    was
O  CD    0.6
O  NN    percent
O  IN    above
O  NNP    April
O  CC    and
O  CD    3.5
O  NN    percent
O  IN    above
O  NNP    July
O  NN    1988.


O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  JJR    Higher
O  NNS    prices
O  IN    during
O  NNP    July
O  IN    for
O  NN    feeder
O  NNS    cattle
O  CC    and
O  NNS    calves
O  ,    ,
O  NN    gasoline
O  CC    and
O  NN    building
O  NNS    materials
O  VBD    were
O  RB    partially
O  VBN    offset
O  IN    by
O  JJR    lower
O  NN    feed
O  NNS    prices
O  ,    ,
O  ''    '
O  ''    '
O  DT    the
O  NN    report
O  NN    said.


O  VBN    Based
O  IN    on
O  DT    the
O  JJ    preliminary
O  NNS    figures
O  ,    ,
O  DT    the
O  NN    price
O  NN    index
O  IN    for
O  NN    livestock
O  CC    and
O  NN    livestock
O  NNS    products
O  IN    as
O  DT    a
O  NN    group
O  VBD    declined
O  CD    0.6
O  NN    percent
O  IN    from
O  NNP    June
O  TO    to
O  NNP    July
O  CC    but
O  RB    still
O  VBD    averaged
O  CD    6.1
O  NN    percent
O  IN    above
O  JJ    last
O  NN    year
O  POS    's
O  NN    figure.


O  JJ    Overall
O  NN    crop
O  NNS    prices
O  VBD    declined
O  CD    2.9
O  NN    percent
O  IN    from
O  JJ    last
O  NN    month
O  CC    and
O  CD    2.2
O  NN    percent
O  IN    from
O  NNP    July
O  NN    1988.


O  DT    The
O  JJ    all-fruit
O  NN    index
O  VBD    was
O  IN    down
O  CD    20
O  NN    percent
O  IN    from
O  JJ    last
O  NN    month
O  CC    and
O  CD    19
O  NN    percent
O  IN    from
O  DT    a
O  NN    year
O  NN    ago.


O  DT    The
B-ORG  NNP    U.S.
I-ORG  NNP    Department
I-ORG  IN    of
I-ORG  NN    Agriculture
O  VBZ    says
O  PRP    it
O  VBZ    's
O  VBG    working
O  IN    on
O  DT    a
O  NN    way
O  TO    to
O  VB    find
O  IN    out
O  WRB    how
O  JJ    much
O  NN    soil
O  VBZ    is
O  VBG    blowing
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  NN    wind.



O  DT    The
B-ORG  NNP    USDA
O  VBZ    says
O  JJ    semi-arid
O  TO    to
O  JJ    humid
O  NNS    croplands
O  IN    outside
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    Great
I-LOC  NNP    Plains
O  RB    often
O  VBD    threatened
O  IN    by
O  NN    wind
O  NN    erosion
O  VBP    include
O  JJ    much
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
O  JJ    southeastern
O  NN    seaboard
O  :    ;
O  JJ    sandy
O  CC    and
O  JJ    organic
O  NN    soil
O  NNS    areas
O  IN    of
B-LOC  NNP    Michigan
O  ,    ,
B-LOC  NNP    Wisconsin
O  CC    and
B-LOC  NNP    Minnesota
O  :    ;
O  JJ    lakebed
O  NNS    soils
O  IN    of
B-LOC  NNP    Ohio
O  ,    ,
B-LOC  NNP    Michigan
O  ,    ,
B-LOC  NNP    Minnesota
O  CC    and
B-LOC  NNP    North
I-LOC  NNP    Dakota
O  :    ;
O  DT    the
O  NNP    Palouse
O  NN    region
O  IN    of
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    Pacific
I-LOC  NNP    Northwest
O  CC    and
O  JJ    several
O  JJ    irrigated
O  NNS    valleys
O  IN    of
B-LOC  NNP    California.


O  VBG    Rotating
O  NN    grain
O  NNS    crops
O  ,    ,
O  JJ    such
O  IN    as
O  NN    corn
O  IN    with
O  NN    alfalfa
O  ,    ,
O  VBZ    is
O  DT    a
O  JJ    key
O  NN    strategy
O  IN    for
O  VBG    sustaining
O  NN    agriculture
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
O  RB    long
O  NN    run
O  ,    ,
O  VBG    according
O  TO    to
O  DT    a
O  JJ    new
O  NN    study
O  IN    by
O  DT    the
B-ORG  NNP    U.S.
I-ORG  NNP    Department
I-ORG  IN    of
I-ORG  NNP    Agriculture
O  CC    and
B-ORG  NNP    Cornell
I-ORG  NNP    University
O  NN    scientists.



O  PRP    He
O  VBZ    says
O  DT    the
O  NN    study
O  VBZ    analyzes
O  NN    energy
O  VBZ    uses
O  IN    of
O  JJ    various
O  NN    farming
O  NNS    systems
O  ,    ,
O  VBG    including
O  JJ    continuous
O  NN    corn
O  NNS    crops
O  CC    and
O  JJ    various
O  NNS    rotations
O  IN    of
O  NN    grain
O  CC    and
O  NN    legume
O  NN    crops.


O  JJ    Continuous
O  NN    corn
O  MD    can
O  VB    be
O  RB    highly
O  JJ    productive
O  IN    with
O  DT    the
O  NN    use
O  IN    of
O  NN    nitrogen
O  NN    fertilizer
O  ,    ,
O  PRP    he
O  VBZ    says
O  ,    ,
O  VBG    adding
O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  CC    but
O  VBZ    is
O  IN    of
O  JJ    dubious
O  NN    sustainability
O  IN    because
O  IN    of
O  JJ    high
O  JJ    fossil
O  NN    fuel
O  NN    use
O  CC    and
O  NN    soil
O  NN    erosion.
O  ''    '
O  NN    '


O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  IN    On
O  DT    the
O  JJ    other
O  NN    hand
O  ,    ,
O  ''    '
O  ''    '
B-PER  NNP    Heichel
O  VBD    said
O  ,    ,
O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  NN    legumes
O  VBP    are
O  IN    among
O  DT    the
O  RBS    most
O  JJ    efficient
O  NNS    crops
O  VBN    grown
O  IN    in
O  DT    the
B-LOC  NNP    United
I-LOC  NNPS    States
O  ,    ,
O  RB    partly
O  IN    because
O  JJ    little
O  NN    fuel
O  VBZ    is
O  VBN    required
O  TO    to
O  VB    grow
O  NN    them.



O  ``    `
O  ``    `
O  CC    But
O  DT    a
O  NN    crop
O  NN    rotation
O  IN    that
O  NNS    alternates
O  CD    one
O  NN    crop
O  IN    of
O  NNS    soybeans
O  ,    ,
O  WDT    which
O  RB    normally
O  VBZ    requires
O  DT    no
O  NN    nitrogen
O  NN    fertilizer
O  ,    ,
O  IN    with
O  CD    two
O  NNS    crops
O  IN    of
O  NN    corn
O  MD    could
O  VB    reduce
O  JJ    fossil
O  NN    energy
O  VBP    use
O  IN    by
O  CD    26
O  NN    percent.
O  ''    '
O  NN    '


B-ORG  NNP    Congress
O  NNPS    Considers
O  VBG    Paying
O  IN    for
O  NNP    Renovation
O  IN    of
B-PER  NNP    Quayle
O  NNP    Residence


O  IN    By
B-PER  NNP    ALAN
I-PER  NNP    FRAM


B-ORG  NNP    Associated
I-ORG  NNP    Press
O  NNP    Writer


B-ORG  NNP    Congress
O  MD    may
O  VB    provide
O  NN    taxpayer
O  NN    money
O  TO    to
O  NN    remodel
O  NNP    Vice
B-PER  NNP    Dan
I-PER  NNP    Quayle
O  POS    's
O  JJ    official
O  NN    residence
O  TO    to
O  VB    accommodate
O  PP$    his
O  NN    family
O  ,    ,
O  IN    despite
O  JJR    earlier
O  VBZ    plans
O  TO    to
O  VB    fund
O  DT    the
O  NN    work
O  IN    with
O  JJ    private
O  NN    donations.

